Issue priorities
An issue's priority indicates its relative importance. The default priorities are listed below. Both the priorities and their meanings can be customized by your administrator to suit your organization. Learn more about configuring priorities and their descriptions.
Highest
This problem will block progress.
High
Serious problem that could block progress.
Medium
Has the potential to affect progress.
Low
Minor problem or easily worked around.
Lowest
Trivial problem with little or no impact on progress.
