Issue statuses
An issue's status indicates its current place in the project's workflow. Default statuses are created when you create a project from one of our templates. The statuses are recommended starting points for each template, but you can edit or remove them from a workflow to suit your team's need. You can also create your own. Learn more about configuring statuses and their descriptions.
Here's a list of the statuses that come with JIRA products, depending on what projects you've created on your site.
Open
The issue is open and ready for the assignee to start work on it.
In Progress
This issue is being actively worked on at the moment by the assignee.
Done
Work has finished on the issue.
To Do
The issue has been reported and is waiting for the team to action it.
In Review
The assignee has carried out the work needed on the issue, and it needs peer review before being considered done.
Under review
A reviewer is currently assessing the work completed on the issue before considering it done.
Approved
A reviewer has approved the work completed on the issue and the issue is considered done.
Cancelled
Work has stopped on the issue and the issue is considered done.
Rejected
A reviewer has rejected the work completed on the issue and the issue is considered done.
Reopened
This issue was once resolved, but the resolution was deemed incorrect. From here, issues are either marked assigned or resolved.
Resolved
A resolution has been taken, and it is awaiting verification by reporter. From here, issues are either reopened, or are closed.
Closed
The issue is considered finished. The resolution is correct. Issues which are closed can be reopened.


References-->
https://confluence.atlassian.com/adminjiracloud/issue-statuses-priorities-and-resolutions-973500867.html

https://www.guru99.com/defect-life-cycle.html
